Finding Aid for the Kathy Sawyer Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Jupiter
  - Ganymede – notes, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Io – notes, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Jupiter – imaging (1) (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Jupiter – imaging (2) (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Outer Planets/Asteroids
  - Outer Planets
    - Voyager, 1989-1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Voyager 2, Neptune – draft, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Cassini – notes, 1997 (1) (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Cassini – notes, 1997 (2) (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Cassini – notes, 1997 (3) (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Cassini Mission – Rebuttal, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Pluto – notes, drafts, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - The Planetary Report – “Pieces of the Sky”, November/December 1991 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - The Washington Post – “Shooting back at Space Rocks?”, March 30, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Summary report of Near-Earth-object interception workshop, August 31, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Ida and its Moon, Asteroid-Earth collision modeled, November 1994 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Toutatis press release, October 5, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Voyager Images (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Asteroids
    - Asteroids, April-September 1996 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Proof of story ASTEROID, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Greenland Meteorite, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Asteroids, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Asteroids, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Killer Rocks Press Conference Notes, July 27, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Pioneer spacecraft passing through the asteroid belt (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Asteroid Landing – notes, 2001 (1) (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Asteroid Landing – notes, 2001 (2) (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Asteroid Landing – notes, 2001 (3) (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Asteroid Landing – notes, 2001 (4) (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Asteroids/Comets
  - Asteroids
    - Asteroid notes, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Asteroid – Earth bound – notes (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Asteroid – images (1) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Comets
    - Comet S-L9, Jupiter Inspection – notes, 1993-1994 (1) (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Comet S-L9, Jupiter Inspection – notes, 1993-1994 (2) (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Comet S-L9, Jupiter Inspection – notes, 1993-1994 (3) (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Comet S-L9, Jupiter Inspection – notes, 1993-1994 (4) (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Comet S-L9, Jupiter Inspection – notes, 1993-1994 (5) (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Comet S-L9, Jupiter Inspection – notes, 1993-1994 (6) (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - David Levy, notes 1994 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Comet Ring Discovery, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Hyakutake – notes, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Stardust – notes, 1998-1999 (1) (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Stardust – notes, 1998-1999 (2) (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Extra Solar/Cosmology
  - Cosmology
    - Saul Perlmutter (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - End of universe (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Planets
    - Extra solar (1) (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Extra solar (2) (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Extra solar (3) (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Keck/Marcy (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Oldest planet (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Astronomy photos (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Astronomy photos (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Space Science
  - Misc. Solar System – notes (1) (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Solar System – notes (2) (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Age of Universe – notes, drafts, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Astronomy – clips, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Astronomy – notes (1) (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Astronomy – notes (2) (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - UFOs (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - NASA – notes, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - NASA – Budget, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Hubble Article for Washingtonian, 2006 (1) (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Hubble Article for Washingtonian, 2006 (2) (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Hubble Article for Washingtonian, 2006 (3) (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Hubble Briefings for Article, 1999, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous Space Science
  - Quasars – notes, 1989-1995 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Quark – notes, 1994 (1) (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Quark – notes, 1994 (2) (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Adaptive Optics – notes, drafts, 1996 (1) (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Adaptive Optics – notes, drafts, 1996 (2) (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Buckey Balls – notes, drafts, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Cambrian Rollover – notes, drafts, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - DNA Computing, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Dark Energy/Cosmos – Perlmutter Text, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Baruch Blumberg Profile – notes, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Kursk Submarine Accident, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Leo Frank Interview Contacts (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Iridium Satellites, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Dreamtime, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Hawaii Energy Lab – notes, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Columbia Search/Hearings, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Space Station – notes, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Maps from Vice President (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous Space Science/Climate Change
  - Misc. Space Science
    - Gore-Triana, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - FUSE Satellite, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Sun Storms – notes (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Advanced War Technology (1) (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Advanced War Technology (2) (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Ballistic Missile Defense – notes (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Climate Change
    - GOES Satellite – notes, copy 1993 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Global Climate Change notes, 1995-1996 (1) (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Global Climate Change – notes, 1995-1996 (2) (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Global Climate Change – notes, 1995-1996 (3) (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Hurricane Modeling – notes, copy, 1995 (1) (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Hurricane Modeling – notes, copy, 1995 (2) (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Hurricane Modeling – notes, copy, 1995 (3) (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Blizzard of 1996 – notes, copy, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Weather, 1996 Olympics – notes, copy (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Weather, 1996 Olympics – notes (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Extreme Life, Biology
  - Space Effects on Human Body—Millie Mission, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Giant Squid, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Methane Ice Worms, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Early Signs of Life, 1997-2001 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Early Signs of Life, 1997-2001 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Extremophiles & Vents, 1997-2001 (1) (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Extremophiles & Vents, 1997-2001 (2) (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Extremophiles & Vents, 1997-2001 (3) (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Exobiology – notes, research (1) (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Exobiology – notes, research (2) (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Exobiology – notes, research (3) (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Extreme life, late 1990s-2003 (1) (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Extreme life, late 1990s-2003 (2) (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Astrobiology Research, 1998-2002 (1) (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Astrobiology Research, 1998-2002 (2) (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Health/Freelance—Johnny Cash
  - NIC – Poisson – clips, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - NIC – Poisson – Clinical Trials, 1994 (1) (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - NIC – Poisson – Clinical Trials, 1994 (2) (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - NIC – Poisson – Clinical Trials, 1994 (3) (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - NIC – Poisson – Clinical Trials, 1994 (4) (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - NIC – Poisson – Clinical Trials, 1994 (5) (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - NIC – Poisson – Clinical Trials, 1994 (6) (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - NIC – Poisson – Clinical Trials, 1994 (7) (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - NIC – Poisson – Clinical Trials, 1994 (8) (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - NIC – Poisson – Clinical Trials, 1994 (9) (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - NIC – Poisson – contact notes, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Cash – notes, interviews (1) (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Cash – notes, interviews (2) (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Cash – notes, interviews (3) (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Cash – notes, interviews (4) (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Cash – bios (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Cash – clippings (1) (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Cash – clippings (2) (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Freelance –Johnny Cash
  - Cash – Show 1 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Cash – Show 7 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Cash – Show 7 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Cash – Show 10 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Cash – Show 14 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Cash – Show 15 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Cash – incomplete scripts (1) (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Cash – incomplete scripts (2) (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Cash – incomplete scripts (3) (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Cash – incomplete scripts (4) (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Cash – incomplete scripts (5) (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Cash – incomplete scripts (6) (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Cash – incomplete scripts (7) (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Freelance –National Geographic
  - Nat Geo – Universe, 1999 – notes, drafts (1) (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Nat Geo – Universe, 1999 – notes, drafts (2) (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Nat Geo – Universe, 1999 – notes, drafts (3) (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Nat Geo – Universe, 1999 – notes, drafts (4) (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Nat Geo – Universe, 1999 – notes, drafts (5) (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Mars Article for Nat Geo (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Nat Geo – Mars, 2000 – notes, drafts (1) (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Nat Geo – Mars, 2000 – notes, drafts (2) (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Nat Geo – Mars, 2000 – notes, drafts (3) (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Nat Geo – Mars, 2000 – notes, drafts (4) (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Nat Geo – Mars, 2000 – notes, drafts (5) (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Nat Geo – Mars, 2000 – notes, drafts (6) (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Nat Geo – Mars, 2000 – notes, drafts (7) (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Freelance/Style Section and Miscellaneous Features
  - Nat Geo – Mars, 2000 – notes, drafts (8) (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Nat Geo – Mars, 2000 – notes, drafts (9) (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Nat Geo – Mars, 2000 – proofs (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Nat Geo – Mars, 2000 – Final Copy (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - National Geographic, Vol. 194, No. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - NASA Budget – notes (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Style Section and Miscellaneous Features
    - Stringer File (Harwood), 1994 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Fundamentalism/Christian Right Series, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Maran Feature for Style Section, 2000 (1) (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Maran Feature for Style Section, 2000 (2) (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Maran Feature for Style Section, 2000 (3) (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Confederate Flag Feature, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Watching Paint Dry for Style Section, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Books/Miscellaneous Freelance
  - Johnny Cash Interview Notes (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - “Pork” Notes (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - NASP—Technology Transition Program (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - The Soviet Manned Space Program (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Tethered Satellite System Data Reference Book (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - MIR Hardware Heritage (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Julian Bond (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - VISTA Article, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Articles
  - March 1965 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - April 1965 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - May 1965 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - June 1965 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - July 1965 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - August-September 1965 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - October 1965 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - November 1965 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - December 1965 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - January 1966 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - February 1966 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - April 1966 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - June-July 1966 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - August 1966 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - September 1966 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - October 1966 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - December 1966 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - January 1967 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - February-March 1967 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - April-May 1967 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - June 1967 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - July-August 1967 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - November 1967 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - January-March 1968 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - April-May 1968 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - June-July 1968 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - August 1968 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - October-November 1968 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - 1968 ‘Hippies’ Series (Box 35, Folder 29)
- Articles
  - January 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - March 1969 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - April 1969 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - May 1969 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - June 1969 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - July 1969 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - August 1969 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - September 1969 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - October 1969 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - November-December 1969 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - January-April 1970 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - May-October 1970 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - November 1970 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - January-May 1971 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - July-September 1971 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - October-December 1971 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - January-April 1972 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - May-December 1972 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - January 1973 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - February-July 1973 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - December 1973 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - February 1974 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - July 1974 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - October 1974 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - 1975 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Articles
  - January-June 1976 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - July-December 1976 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - January 1977 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - February 1977 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - May 1984 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - August 1984 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - October 1984 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - December 1984 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - January 1985 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - February 1985 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - March-April 1985 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - May 1985 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - June 1985 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - July-August 1985 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - September-November 1985 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - January 1986 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - February 1986 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - March 1986 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - April 1986 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - May 1986 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - June 1986 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - July 1986 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - August 1986 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - September 1986 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - October 1986 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - November 1986 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - December 1986 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Articles
  - October 1978 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - November 1978 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - December 1978 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - October 1979 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - November 1979 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - December 1979 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - 1980 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - January 1981 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - February 1981 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - March 1981 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - August 1982 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - December 1982 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - February 1983 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - May 1983 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - September 1983 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - December 1983 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Articles
  - January 1993 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - May 1993 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - June 1993 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - August 1993 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - September 1993 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - November 1993 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - December 1993 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - January-February 1994 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - April 1994 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - May-June 1994 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - July-August 1994 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - October 1994 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - November 1994 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - December 1994 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - January 1995 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - February 1995 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - March 1995 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - May 1995 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - June 1995 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - July 1995 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - October 1995 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - November 1995 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - December 1995 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - January 1996 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - February 1996 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - March 1996 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - April 1996 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - May 1996 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - August 1996 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - December 1996 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - January 1997 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - February 1997 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - March 1997 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - April 1997 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - June 1997 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Articles
  - July 1997 (1) (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - July 1997 (2) (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - August 1997 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - September 1997 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - October 1997 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - November 1997 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - December 1997 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - February 1998 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - March 1998 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - April 1998 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - May 1998 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - June 1998 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - July 1998 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - August 1998 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - September 1998 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - October 1998 (1) (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - October 1998 (2) (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - November 1998 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - December 1998 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - January 1999 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - February 1999 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - March 1999 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - April 1999 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - May 1999 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - July 1999 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - August 1999 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - September 1999 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - October 1999 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - November 1999 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - December 1999 (Box 40, Folder 30)
- Articles/The Tennessean
  - Articles
    - February 2000 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - July 2000 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - January 2003 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - February 2003 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - March 2003 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - April 2003 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - May 2003 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - June 2003 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - July 2003 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - August 2003 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - September 2003 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - October 2003 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - November 2003 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - December 2003 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - January 2004 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - February 2004 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - August 2007 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Articles—Undated The Tennessean (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - The Tennessean
    - Tennessean, March 1970 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Tennessean, April 1971 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Tennessean, August 1973 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- The Washington Post
  - July 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - August 1975 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - September 1975 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - October-December 1975 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - January-February 1976 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - March 1976 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - April 1976 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - May 1976 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - June-September 1976 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- The Washington Post
  - October – December 1976 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - January – February 1977 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - December 1982 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - January – April 1983 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - July – November 1983 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - January 1986 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - February 1986 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - June 1986 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - August 3, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - August 27-31, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- The Washington Post
  - September 1988 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - October 1988 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - June 1988 – August 1989 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - April 1990 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - September 1995 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - March 1997 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - July 1999 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Oversized Images/Slides
  - Photos
    - Kathy Sawyer at Nashville Airport (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - “Mars Layers” (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Slides
    - Mars—The Planet (1) (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Mars—The Planet (2) (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Mars Pathfinder/Sojourner: Return to the Red Planet (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Cassini/Huygens (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Voyager Mission to Neptune (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Voyager Mission to Uranus (1) (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Voyager Mission to Uranus (2) (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Voyager Mission to Saturn (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Voyager Mission to Jupiter (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Far Galaxies (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Inside the Space Station (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Buckeyballs (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - The Buford Pusser Story
    - “Everybody’s Out to Get Buford Now” (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Audio Cassettes
  - Cassettes
    - JPL May 22/23, 2000; Dan McLeesh, Arden Albee, and W Albee talk (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - JPL May 23, 2000; Albee, cont. (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - B. Johnson re e-mails (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - B. Malin interview – M’s life; the failures and risks, May 19, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Malin 3 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Goldin, Roger Angell, Lon Friedne – AAAS, February 7, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Edgett and Malin Mars –, May 18th (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - O’Keefe Press Club/Greenfield (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Mars/Water Press Conference, HQ Malin et al, June 22, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Muon anti standard model (no fit), February 1, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Sex in Space (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Cosmology (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - SR-71 and NASP/Dryden interview (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Don Kutyna, April 7, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Loren Thompson, January 28, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Keck-Marcy-Friday night (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Hoot Gibson, December 12, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Adam Reiss SN 1.72 (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - OSNOS; Hatfield – NYC (w/ soft skull), February 23 (Box 47, Folder 34)
    - Hatfield (1) (Box 47, Folder 35)
    - July 7 foam impact test/Hubbard (Box 47, Folder 36)
    - Logsdon, Carr on RCC, May 14, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 37)
    - Chuck Brown/camera; Oberman 6/26 (Box 47, Folder 38)
    - Brian the Rover Driver (Mars landing); Dust guys (Box 47, Folder 39)
    - Mike Meyer, June 8, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 40)
    - Mike Carr – end of tape (Box 47, Folder 41)
    - Italian Scientist Deserting Meteorite – Fall-Spring 2001 (weird) (Box 47, Folder 42)
    - Worm guy Lefkowski – Laura Maran – May 1/ Terri on worms (Box 47, Folder 43)
    - Talone/SS – November 6, 1998/ NASA TV – Annie crew arrival (Box 47, Folder 44)
    - August 25, 2000 – OSTP, etc. Iriduin (Box 47, Folder 45)
    - NASA/Hawes (astron.) (Box 47, Folder 46)
    - Wallace, May 1, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 47)
    - Sox, et al – re Soya landing/ Jack at KSC (Box 47, Folder 48)
    - Sheila Widnell (Box 47, Folder 49)
    - Dressler AAS 1999/ Press panel – Kirchner – Start Dressler (Box 47, Folder 50)
    - Skunk works X-33 (Box 47, Folder 51)
    - M.C. Tour (Box 47, Folder 52)
    - Tour day 2 (9/18) JSC sims, etc. (Box 47, Folder 53)
    - Pate – Cornell/ Gene Covert (Box 47, Folder 54)
    - Guford Stevor, Wallace (Box 47, Folder 55)
    - OEX box briefing – April 24, Hallock (Box 47, Folder 56)
    - O’Conner 3/14 (30 min)/MIT guy/Boeing guys re alum (Box 47, Folder 57)
    - Michael Leinbach KSC 3/28; Time McKelvey KSC OEX box dubbing – April 3, 2003/Barry re canier panel (Box 47, Folder 58)
    - Mars rock – magnetite entries, etc, February 22, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 59)
    - Hubbard 6-12/ Foam test- San Antonio, Hubbard (Box 47, Folder 60)
    - Andrew Steele at Carnegie, May 24, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 61)
    - Carnegie Institution, October, 4/04 – Mega, Steelie, etc. – Svalsbord (Box 47, Folder 62)
    - Gehman April 8 Blumberg (Box 47, Folder 63)
    - 1997 AAAS Annual Meeting – Implications of the Possibility of Life on Mars (1) (Box 47, Folder 64)
    - 1997 AAAS Annual Meeting – Implications of the Possibility of Life on Mars (2) (Box 47, Folder 65)
    - Gehman Hearing April 8 – II (Box 47, Folder 66)
- Audio Cassettes
  - Gehman April 8 Hearing III (ride) (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Gehman Hearing April 23 – NASA Alum (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Gehman Hearing April 23 II – Aging aircraft (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Gehman Hearing April 23 III – Aging and Vaughn (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Golder Press Club, June 20, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Keck 1st tape, frozen shutter (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Keck I (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Tape II Keck (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Keck III Marcy (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Permutter, August 31, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Tape one – Perlmutter, October 6, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Perlmutter II (Fri) Gerson and Peter (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Saul Perlmutter III (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Perlmutter IV (Sat), October 9, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Gehman March 26 KSC III (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Gehman briefing, April 15 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Gehman briefing, May 6, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Gehman hearing KSC III (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Gehman (4) RCC Slag (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Gehman Hearing Part 2, March 17 (Box 48, Folder 20)